{
    "subject": "resource/Sant'Antonio_di_Gallura",
    "predicate": "property/province",
    "object": "resource/Province_of_Olbia-Tempio",
    "human_readable": "Sant'Antonio di Gallura is located in the Province of Olbia-Tempio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9617984294891357,
            "question": "Is Sant'Antonio di Gallura part of a province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9575544595718384,
            "question": "Which province includes Sant'Antonio di Gallura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9467090368270874,
            "question": "Where is Sant'Antonio di Gallura located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9428880214691162,
            "question": "Can you tell me the province where Sant'Antonio di Gallura is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9315473437309265,
            "question": "Sant'Antonio di Gallura is found in which Italian province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870308995246887,
            "question": "What is the name of the Province that Sant'Antonio di Gallura is part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.865105152130127,
            "question": "To which province does Sant'Antonio di Gallura belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8561615943908691,
            "question": "What is the name of the province that Sant'Antonio di Gallura belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.765235424041748,
            "question": "What geographical region encompasses Sant'Antonio di Gallura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.506543755531311,
            "question": "In what administrative division is Sant'Antonio di Gallura found?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sant'Antonio di Gallura is located in the Province of Olbia-Tempio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3564_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What geographical region encompasses Sant'Antonio di Gallura?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3564_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the province that Sant'Antonio di Gallura belongs to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3564_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which province does Sant'Antonio di Gallura belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3564_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3564_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that Sant'Antonio di Gallura is located in the province of Olbia-Tempio, which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}